<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="/bloom.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>Bloom Consulting Group</title>
    <link>http://www.bloomconsultinggroup.com/</link>
    <description />
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>5 Mar 2016 20:13:23 Z</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Bloom-hones-focus-on-security</guid>
      <title>Bloom hones focus on security</title>
      <pubDate>18 Jan 2016 16:00:06 Z</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.securitysystemsnews.com/article/bloom-hones-focus-security</link>
	  <description>
      REDMOND, Wash.—If you don’t understand how a modern executive works, your security solution is doomed, according to Heather Zindel, CEO, Bloom Consulting Group.

      Bloom, based here, is a developer of enterprise mobile applications, that is focused on helping users build remote/mobile security operations centers. The company is comprised of business consultants, architects and software engineers.
      
      Bloom was recently honored, along with its partner Microsoft, on the development of its Microsoft Advanced Patrol Platform (MAPP), which helps police patrol teams with a mobile command center that delivers critical information and intelligence once only accessible at a physical command center.
      
      Modern executives tend to “move across a number of devices during the day.” To be truly useful, applications need to work across a variety of form factors well, she said.
      
      Bloom’s role is not to integrate, it’s to aggregate, Zindel emphasized. “We provide a single-pane-of-glass view,” she said.
      
      In business for seven years, Zindel said her company has seen a “surge in demand for modern applications that deliver insight and aggregate data.”
      
      “We anticipate accelerated growth over next two years, and most of that growth will come out of the security industry,” she said.  
      
      To ensure that “key topics get debated at the board level,” Zindel recently assembled an advisory board made up of security and high tech industry experts, including Shawn Usher, president and CEO, Sparkhound; Ray O’Hara, EVP of AS Solution; and Robert Hile, director of Enterprise Command Centers for SureView Systems.
      
      “Our mission to help executives specifically in the security industry modernize the business of security,” Zindel said.
      
      Systems integrators and manufacturers tend to be focused at the operational level. But, program managers and CSOs are dealing with an overwhelming amount of data and they need strong partners to help them turn that data into useful information, she said.
		</description>
    </item>
	
	<item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Bloom-Consulting-delivers-bleeding-edge-tech-to-security-execs</guid>
      <title>Bloom Consulting delivers 'bleeding-edge' tech to security execs</title>
      <pubDate>15 Feb 2016 16:00:06 Z</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.securityinfowatch.com/article/12174810/bloom-consulting-delivers-bleeding-edge-tech-to-security-execs</link>
	  	<description>For years the security industry has worked to solve the quandary of how to best deliver the most relevant information to right people at the right time. While various security management software platforms have done their part to streamline the massive amounts of data generated by surveillance cameras, access card readers and various other sensors an organization may have into an easily digestible format for security operations personnel, there has been little innovation in terms of how this and other information from the field is aggregated and presented to security executives and other senior-level managers.
		</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>